Team: Australia
  Total Medals when Host: 57
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 363

Team: Brazil
  Total Medals when Host: 17
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 117

Team: China
  Total Medals when Host: 93
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 589

Team: France
  Total Medals when Host: 64
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 327

Team: Great Britain
  Total Medals when Host: 63
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 395

Team: Japan
  Total Medals when Host: 58
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 284

Team: South Korea
  Total Medals when Host: 32
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 211

Team: Spain
  Total Medals when Host: 22
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 141

Team: United States
  Total Medals when Host: 272 (99 in 1996)
  Total Medals when Non-Host: 946

